this problem has
a few different steps we want to select
dog from pets and add that return value
to the my pets array
then we're going to print the value of
my pets
in a sentence that matches the expected
output we were given
on line 2 you can see that we originally
created the my
pets array with two elements however on
line three
we invoked the array pop method
and remove the last element of the array
let's quickly take a look at what the my
pets array looks like now
you can see that after removal of the
second element
the my pets array has only one element
fish
so the first step of this problem is to
select the string dog
from the pet's array
we can see that dog is the second
element in the pets array
and because arrays have a zero-based
index we can select
dog using element reference at
index one and let's output that
the problem asks us to add the return
value of that element reference
to the mypet's array
in order to add an element to the end of
an array
ruby provides us the array push method
and we can pass in this string dog
which our element reference returns
as an argument to push
push will then add that element on to
the end of the my pets array
let's output my pets to see that
and now we have a two element array with
dog being the second element
so we successfully modified the my pets
array with the array push method
and now we want to match the expected
output we were
given
again we'll use element reference here
to
access each element of this two element
array
so we know we want to access the first
element of the array with index zero
and the second and last element of the
array
dog with index one
and we've achieved the expected output